威尔 · 森坦斯: 好了，伙计们，我们开始吧，我们开始吧,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: All right folks,
so here we go, let's jump in,
一号线，我们要对伊森做什么。
line one, what are we doing to Ethan.
这句话很奇怪，第一行，我们在做什么，逗号，给伊桑。
That phrasing was very strange, line one,
what are we doing, comma, to Ethan.
[笑声]演讲者2: 我宣布
&gt;&gt; [LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: I'm declaring
外部函数。
the function outer.
威尔 · 森特斯: 太好了，谢谢你，伊森,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Excellent,
thank you, Ethan,
就是这样，外面，好的，保存，下一行，伊森。
there it is, Outer, okay,
Save, next line, Ethan.
说话人2: 然后我们声明常量 myNewFunction。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: And then we are declaring
the constant myNewFunction.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 非常好，我的新功能,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Very nice,
myNewFunction,
知道里面放什么吗，伊森？
any idea what to store in there, Ethan?
讲者2: 还没有。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Not yet.
威尔 · 森特斯: 不，因为我们必须继续前进，做什么？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: No,
because we've gotta go ahead and do what?
演讲者2: 我们必须叫外层？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: We have to call Outer?
威尔 · 森特斯: 你说得非常完美，完全正确,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: You put it perfectly,
exactly,
我们得把 Outer 放到调用堆栈上。
we've got to go and
put Outer on the call stack.
它在调用堆栈上，总是在底部得到全局。
There it is on the call stack,
always got global on the bottom.
一个全局执行上下文，多个函数级执行上下文。
One global execution context,
many function level execution contexts.
它现在还没有初始化，我们出发运行 Outer，没错,
It's uninitialized for now while we
head off and run Outer, that's right,
各位，深呼吸，它来了。
everybody, take that deep breath,
it's coming.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 我们必须执行 Outer，它的结果，当我们排序
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: We've got to execute
Outer, its results when we sort of
在对 myNewFunction 进行排序时，myNewFunction 是返回的值。
myNewFunction is returned values
when we sort myNewFunction.
我们需要一个全新的？
We need a brand new?
演讲者3: 执行上下文！
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Execution context!
威尔 · 森特斯: 太好了，谢谢你，马克，谢谢大家，给你。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Beautiful, thank you
Mark, thank you to everybody, here it is.
我要试着画出来，看这个，我要试着画出来
I'm going to try and draw,
look at this, I'm going to try and
这次把另一条线画直。
draw the other line straight this time.
这不像往常那么糟糕，对吧，不像往常那么糟糕。
That's not as bad as usual,
right, not as bad as usual.
好了，我们开始吧
Okay, into it we go and
首先在我们当地的记忆中
in our local memory first
我们拯救的东西 Kayla？
thing we save, Kayla?
演讲者4: 我们要声明一个计数器变量为零。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: We're going to
declare a counter variable to zero.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 是的，发送到0，字面意思是，人们,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, send it to 0,
that literally means, people,
它曾经让我困惑，我曾经认为。
it used confuse me and I used to think.
也许这就像是说计数器是0。
Maybe it's like just sort
of saying counter is 0.
不是字面意思是我们接受了那个标签那个词,
No, literally we took that label,
that word,
放到电脑的0和1内存里。
put it in the computer's memory 0s and 1s.
拉出那个0，把它放进电脑的存储器，它绝对是存储的。
Pull that 0, put it in the computer's
memory, it is absolutely stored.
好了，下一句，布莱登，我们现在该怎么做？
Okay, next line, Braden,
what are we to say to do here?
这是一句有趣的台词，但是希望很清楚。
It's a funny sort of single line,
but it's hopefully clear.
扬声器2: 所以你声明了函数增量计数器。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: So you're declaring
the function increment counter.
威尔 · 森特斯: 很漂亮，现在我要用不同的颜色来定义它。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Beautiful, now I'm going
to do it definition in a different color.
Braden 这个函数是不是被挖空了,
Braden, is this function being cored,
被调用，被运行，还是我们要用它做点别的事情？
being invoked, being run right now, or are
we instead doing something else with it?
演讲者2: 我们正在用它做其他的事情。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: We're doing
something else with it.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 当然，我们不会运行它,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Absolutely,
we are not running it,
不会接我们的电话。
is not going on our call stacks up here.
相反，我们抓住它，用它做什么，布莱登？
Instead we grabbing it and
doing what with it, Braden?
演讲者2: 把它返回到 myNewFunction。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Returning
it to myNewFunction.
绝对的，把它返回到 myNewFunction。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Absolutely,
returning it out to myNewFunction.
它将是调用 outer 和
It's going to be the output
of calling outer, and
我们要把它存在我的新功能里。
we're gonna store it in myNewFunction.
再次强调，它诞生于 incrementCounter，但我们不会再这样称呼它了。
Again, it was born as incrementCounter,
but we're not gonna call it that anymore.
这就是它的诞生，这是它最初的名字。
That was its birth,
thatt's sort of Its original name.
现在它已经被返回，并被存储为 myNewFunction。
Now it's been returned out and
it's now stored as myNewFunction.
人们，这个执行环境和其中的一切，会发生什么？
People, this execution context and
everything in it, what happens to it?
删除，消失，一个线程编织，它编织出来
Deleted, gone, a thread wove in and
it wove out and
执行上下文被删除。
the execution context is deleted.
希望那里不会太乱，我们可以清楚地看到这一点，[声音]走了。
Hope that's not too messy there,
we can see this clearly, [SOUND] gone.
在调用堆栈上发生了什么？
What happens to on
the call stack everybody?
弹掉了我应该说得更清楚点,
It's popped off,
I should have made it clearer,
popped 就是从堆栈中取出一些东西，这只是用来移除它的一个比较好的词。
popped is to take something off a stack,
it's just a fancy word for removing it.
而 push 是添加到堆栈中的。
And push is to add on to the stack.
所以在堆栈中添加对函数的调用堆栈,
So add on to a stack, in this case,
a stack of calls to functions,
运行的功能，已经消失了。
running of functions, has gone.
现在我们回到全球动力局，我们碰到什么了，杰夫？
And we're back out to global,
where we hit what line, Jeff?
我们在全球范围内遇到的那条线是什么？
What is that line we hit in global?
演讲者2: 我们称之为 myNewFunction。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: We call myNewFunction.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 绝对的，就我们的调用堆栈而言，杰夫,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Absolutely, and
in terms of our call stack, Jeff,
会发生什么？
what's gonna happen?
演讲者2: 创建一个新的执行上下文。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Create
a new execution context.
Will Sentance: 是的，还有我们要添加的所有工具堆栈。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, and all the tool
stack that we are going to add.
讲者2: MyNewFunction 威尔 · 森特斯: 是的,
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: MyNewFunction.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah,
对 myNewFunction 的调用，完美，漂亮的笔迹。
the call to myNewFunction,
perfect, nice handwriting.
全新的执行环境,
All right, brand new execution context,
我把你们从伤痛中拯救出来，那从来都不管用。
I saved you all from injury go,
that never works.
伤病走了，我们走了，什么是我们的
Injury go and we go and what is our
作为我们的本地记忆？
line of code as our local memory?
我们在这个函数里面碰到的那行代码是什么，马克？
What is that line of code that we
hit inside of this function, Mark?
它现在被称为 myNewFunction，但它是作为递增计数器而诞生的。
It's now called myNewFunction, but
it was born as increment counter.
我们的眼睛会慢慢向上移动，乔布斯不会这么做。
Our eyes are gonna creep back up the page,
jobs is not doing that.
它实际上保存了这个函数的代码
It has literally the code of that
function saved over here, and
密码就是，确切的词，马克？
that code is, the exact words, Mark?
Mynewfunction 的代码中的确切词是什么,
What are the exact that words
of the code of myNewFunction,
前递增计数器？
formerly increment counter?
确切的代码是什么？
What's the exact code it's gonna run?
事实上，我得把这个交给托德。
Actually, I've got to
get this one to Todd.
说话者2: 是的，计数器 + + 将句子: 计数器 + + ，干得好,
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Yeah, Counter ++
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Counter ++, well done,
托德，没错，这是计数器 + + 。
Todd, exactly, there it is counter ++.
绿色是我的查找颜色，我首先要看哪里，托德？
Green is my look-up color,
where do I look first, Todd?
演讲者2: 是的，所以你看看你的本地记忆。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Yeah, so
you look in your local memory.
句子: 我找到反了吗？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Do I find counter?
讲者二: 不要。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Do not.
威尔 · 桑特斯: 托德，我在哪里运行我的新函数？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Where am I
running myNewFunction, Todd?
讲者2: 在全球。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: In the global.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 所以直觉告诉我，我在哪里
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: And so everything
intuitively would say where do I
看下一个，托德？
look next, Todd?
演讲者2: 在全局记忆中。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: In the global memory.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 在全球，谢谢你，伙计。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: In global,
thank you, man.
我在全球找到柜台吗？
Do I find counter in global?
讲者二: 没有。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: No.
威尔 · 森特斯: 绝对不行，这是一场灾难[声音]。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Absolutely not,
this is a disaster [SOUND] disaster.
多么奇怪的语言，让我们保存函数，返回它们,
What a strange language that let's
save functions, return them out,
打电话给他们，尝试使用已经消失的数据[声音]。
call them, and try and
use data [SOUND] that's gone.
我们在全局中运行 myNewFunction，我们在 myNewFunction 中查找，没有计数器。
We're running myNewFunction in global,
we look in myNewFunction, no counter.
我们向全球看齐，没有对手。
And we look out to global, no counter.
如果你们已经知道接下来会发生什么，请举手。
Raise your hand if you already know
the answer to what's gonna happen here.
所以不一定清楚，对吧，这是一个谜。
So not necessarily clear,
right, this is a mystery.
谁知道举手的人是否知道呢？
And who knows if the people who
raise their hands even know?
因为这是非常神秘的，我们不完全。
For this is very mysterious,
we don't exactly.
我还能坚持多久，[听起来]很悲伤。
How long can I play it out,
[SOUND] very sad.
天哪这太傻了,
God, this is just silly,
我们没有找到我们的计数器,
we didn't find our counter hmm,
我们为什么要做这些工作？
why would we do all this work?
我可以用多长时间来让这个变得多尴尬啊。
How awkward can I make
this by how long [LAUGH.
为什么我们做这一切的工作，如果只是找不到反？
Why do we do all this work
if only not to find counter?
这是一场灾难，这是一场灾难！
This is a disaster, this is a disaster!
但是，你们知道吗？
And yet, people, you know what?
有些事情我们没有说。
There's something we didn't say here.
结果是，当我接受递增计数器函数定义时,
It turns out that when I took that
increment counter function definition,
所有的代码。
all its code.
并将其作为运行 Outer [ SOUND ]到 myNewFunction 的输出返回。
And returned it out as the output of
running Outer [SOUND] into myNewFunction.
我得到的不仅仅是函数 counter + + 的代码。
I got more than just the code
of the function counter ++.
我得到的不仅仅是保存的代码，还有函数定义。
I got more than just saved code,
the function definition.
各位，我还有一些非常非常有力量的东西，看看这个。
People, I got something so, so
powerful in addition, check this out.
这是非常非常特别的，这是 JavaScript 的一个优雅的特性。
This is very, very special,
this is an elegant feature of JavaScript.
我来处理,
I got this,
当我返回这个函数的时候，我得到了这个函数的其他东西。
when I returned this function out,
I got something else with that function.
当这个函数离开的时候，它带走了所有的东西，并且
As that function left,
it took with it all, and
我们稍后会加上一些注意事项。
we'll add some caveats
on this in a moment.
它带走了保存这个函数的所有周围数据,
It took with it all the surrounding
data from where that function was saved,
它出生的地方，存放的地方。
where it was born, where it was stored.
它抓取了周围的数据，把它带了出来
It grabbed its surrounding data,
and brought it out and
来展示它的旅程。
to sort of show it on its journey.
[声音][笑声]它把周围的数据都带出来了,
[SOUND] [LAUGH] it brought all
that surrounding data out,
在功能的后面加上一个功能。
racing along with a function
on the back of the function.
是的，是的，你喜欢小功能吗？
Yes, yes, you like little functions?
在这一点上，它是滑稽模仿，不是吗？
At this point it's parody, isn't it?
背面的功能，就像一个小背包上的功能。
On the back of the functions,
like a little backpack on the function.
是的，在线观众就像一个背包，这是一个合法的技术术语,
Yes, online viewers, like a backpack,
it's a legitimate technical term,
这是真的。
it's a real thing.
在函数的背面，当函数出来的时候，它带来了它的背面,
On the back of the function, as the
function came out, it brought on its back,
所有周围的数据，有一点需要注意。
all the surrounding data,
little bit of a caveat on that.
它的所有周围数据，带回的功能，附加。
All its surrounding data, brought on
the back of the function, attached.
当我们将之前所知的 incrementCounter 函数保存到
And when we saved that formerly known
as incrementCounter function into
Mynewfunction.
myNewFunction.
我们不仅仅得到了函数定义。
We didn't just get
the function definition.
我们在它上面安装了一个背包
We got attached onto it a backpack from
当这个函数诞生于实时数据时,
when that function was born of live data,
这里的计数器是0。
and there counter is 0.